<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Engineer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_menu">main_menu</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">blablabla</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="text_schedules">Schedule</string>
    <string name="EVENT_LIST_URL">https://cricstat.000webhostapp.com/ved/php/schedule.php</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="schedule">Schedule</string>
    <string name="map">Map</string>

    <!--Home Page String                                             -->
    <string name="action_add_favourite">Add to Favourites</string>
    <string name="action_play_next">Play Next</string>
    <string name="backdrop_title">Engineer</string>
    <string name="backdrop_subtitle">This season top 20 albums</string>
    <string name="committee1">Committee 1</string>
    <string name="Tronix">Tronix</string>
    <string name="Mech">Mechanical</string>
    <string name="Meta">Metallurgy</string>
    <string name="Comp">Comp</string>
    <string name="chem">Reflux</string>
    <string name="Mining">Mining</string>
    <string name="BizWaves">BizWaves</string>
    <string name="Civil">Civil</string>
    <string name="Technites">Technites</string>
    <string name="title_sponsor">Title Sponsor</string>
    <string name="other_sponsors">Other Sponsors</string>
    <string name="prizes_sponsor">Prizes Sponsor</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="about_engi">Back in 2005, the marvels of NITK created a unique platform for the innovative minds to get acquainted to the aces of engineering industry. Multitude of students came together to organize the technical events and clubbed it into one grand glomeration and fondly christened it- ENGINEER, the annual technical symposium of NITK. Challenging the impossibility in the purest form, the Penrose triangle stands as the icon for the fest and so the maxim goes” THINK, CREATE, ENGINEER”.\nThe 14 th edition of Engineer far exceeds its ancestors, the fest emerges to be nationwide celebration, ranking second among India\'s technical fests. Racing its way to zenith, Engineer has become kaleidoscope of exhilaration of various flagship events such as Velocity, Robowar, Tronix Events, Workshops,flasmobs,online coding events with participation from various teams, among many such mind racking challenges. The stage has been enriched with the presence of distinguished speakers like Richard Stallman, Sam Pitrda, Dr Devi Sheet, Sir Anthony James Legett and many more. It has also played host to global organizations such as CERN, MIT Media and Ball Labs. To boost the effective innovation for the society, we also emphasise on Socially conscious Engineering. We also incorporate fun filled events like freefall which serve as pinnacle of attraction. NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY KARNATAKA This wonderful fusion of technical skills with boisterous events will definitely dilate the reasoning of innovative minds and helping them to showcase their talents on a higher platform.</string>
    <string name="foxhunt">Always been a big fan of treasure hunt? What if you get to hunt a Fox? Well, not literally, but here we give you a chance to build your very own receiver antenna and compete with other Teams to hunt the Fox down. And what’s more, you don’t even have to get the materials! We provide you with everything - from the instructions during the workshop to the solder gun! So come one, come all to witness the best of the Tronix Committee!</string>
    <string name="Symphony">Taming a full-size fountain is no easy task. Yet, dozens of participants do exactly that, as they make the fountain dance to the beats of music. Dancing fountains, flashing lights, great music. Whether you win or not, you are guaranteed to have a great time. Participants can trial their circuit on Oct 11. Event is going to be held on Oct 12.</string>
    <string name="Trade_off">India is known for it’s frugal innovation. Show how frugal you can be, when you compromise between time and component costs to arrive at a circuit which gives the desired output? This is not going to be easy though, as you compete with the smartest of students out there. The quickest and smartest survives!</string>
    <string name="TrailBlazer">Set the trail on fire (figuratively, please), as your bot goes around intricate curves following a line and performing tasks on the way. A line-follower event of the next level, Trailblazer attracts some of the most innovative bots from across the country.</string>
    <string name="Light_of_seven">An event in which participants build a light following bot. Seems easy? Prepare to be proved wrong as the number of resources are lowered and its all about that. The simplicity of this event attracts many participants and you will surely be surprised by the techniques used by them.</string>
    <string name="Automata">A treat for computer vision enthusiasts, Automata is a one of it’s kind competition where you are given a live feed from an overhead camera; the challenge is to autonomously make your computer guide your bot under the camera to perform some tasks. It is a timed event, the winner is decided based upon the completed tasks and the time taken.</string>
    <string name="Robowars">Robowars is an event in which participating teams battle it out among themselves with their bots for the numero uno position. The competition is carried out in a tournament format: competitors bring their robots ready to battle and are pitted against their competitors’ robots in one-on-one matches.</string>
    <string name="bot_hockey">Bot Hockey is an exciting and challenging competition featuring two teams with remote controlled robots competing against each other to score goals with a ball. This game is our version of the computer game Ice Hockey and rewards driving skill more than expensive robot.</string>
    <string name="perfect_machine">Perfect machine is a unique competition which tests the skills of the participant in tackling various tasks that are given to them with their bot. Bots have to perform tasks efficiently and effectively to earn as many points as possible in a limited time period.</string>
    <string name="wright_flight">Wright Flight attracts RC plane hobbyists from all over the country with unique and challenging flying tasks. The aim is to design and make a fast, light, wireless remote controlled aircraft to do certain tasks such as loop the loop and payload delivery in the designated area for points.</string>
    <string name="bot_foot">Bot football is a multiplayer game where two players use their wire. less bots to defeat their opponent in a limited time football match.</string>
    <string name="laser_pro">Laser Turret. There is a big display screen in front of two players with RED and BLUE LEDs blinking at random. Every player has a gun with laser attached to it. Each person will try to aim the laser on either BLUE or RED blinking LED.</string>
    <string name="laser_pro2">Laser Harp. This eye-catching project is a harp-like laser device which mainly focuses on playing a harp with laser, as a true MIDI controller. Laser Limbo. Laser limbo in Technites provides just the opportunity to have a fair-flexible game of limbo against your friend and find who is the most flexible.</string>
    <string name="contr">A great implementation of classic Rube Goldberg machine.</string>
    <string name="virt_sand">This was most highly anticipated exhibition made by using Augmented Reality and used projector to implement it.</string>
    <string name="meta_mag">A series of events that prove that metallurgy is a force to be reckoned with. Nylon Interfacial Condensation, Chemical Garden,Rod Climbing Experiment,Mercury Heartbeat,Thermochronic Mug,Heat Treatment of nails,Dry Ice,Freezing experiments</string>
    <string name="mindbend">A thrilling quiz with an interesting blend of pop culture, test your brain cells in this maze of questions that will surely bend your mind!</string>
    <string name="sem_tem">Participate in this guided tour through our labs and get to see how the Scanning and Transmission Electron Microscopes work.</string>
    <string name="constarch">This interactive session shows how crazy of a Non-Newtonian fluid constarch can be!</string>
    <string name="thermite">This extremely stunning visual demo shows the practical side of how welding rails work using the Thermite Welding process.</string>
    <string name="ga">Using pure science and a bit of brute force, embrittlement of Al sheets has never been explained easier in a way that triggers the brain.</string>
    <string name="blast_furnce"><![CDATA[A clay furnace & a low melting point metal such as Pb is all you need to show a successful demonstration.]]></string>
    <string name="foil">Another dramatically stunning experiment to feast your eyes on, this session demonstrates how a simple packaging material like metal foil undergoes amalgamation.</string>
    <string name="col">TEST YOUR KNOWLEDGE IN STRUCTURAL ENGINEERING. DESIGN AND FABRICATE A BRIDGE IN THE MOST INNOVATE WAY POSSIBLE. The event is aimed to improve design and management skills of participants. And also provides an opportunity to learn fabrication processes.</string>
    <string name="mind_bend"><![CDATA[MINDBOGGLING QUESTIONS, TESTS YOUR APTITUDE AND REASONING, FUN & EXCITING ROUNDS. The event will be an amalgamation of visual rounds and written tests, full of interesting and intriguing challenges.]]></string>
    <string name="arch">BUILD SIMPLE, BUT WORKING MODELS FROM DAILY USE ITEMS(POPSICLE STICKS, PAPER ETC.). Civil Engineering is an art; a profession of creative ability and logic. Architect provides an opportunity for participants to unleash their innovation in designing an object of significance and splendour.</string>
    <string name="chem_break">Its the flagship event which is conducted for all newbies i.e. the first year B.Tech, M.Tech, B.Sc and M.Sc and is conducted on the first day of engineer.It consists of a general quiz, a unique \'Picture Connect\' round and a treasure hunt as the final round which is conduted in the Chemical Dept. of NITK!!!</string>
    <string name="idp">IDP aims to enhance interaction with the industry through real time problem solving. Participants are encouraged to take part in groups of 2 or 3. A problem statement is given a week before the event for participants to come with the best possible solutions. On the event day teams present their thoughts before professionals from the concerned industry and startle them!!</string>
    <string name="capture">Taking an image, freezing a moment, reveals how rich reality truly is. Capture is a photo gallery event where you get to show us a moment captured by you, which depicts any science related processes. Describe it with a maximum of 150 words to let us know your thoughts and understanding of what is going on in the image.</string>
    <string name="chem_e_talks">Do you want to meet international academicians, researchers, entrepeneurs and industrialists? Do you want to interact with these dignitaries and gain knowledge through their experience? Then come join us at the Chem E talks and explore the world of chemical engineering and take home an inspiring and encouraging experience at the price of a movie ticket. Below mentioned are the eminent speakers and their achievements and work, who will be enlightning us through their talks.</string>
    <string name="inscr">A flagship event by Computer Science department this INDIVIDUAL online event has attracted participation from some of the top teams like Microsoft, Yahoo, and Stanford, and recieved appreciations from India\'s competitive programmers (including ACM ICPC World Finalists) for its quality. Tie your boots and prove your mettle, write best codes faster than the best coders!!!</string>
    <string name="kode_komb">Three rounds, each being a thrilling mix of coding debugging and puzzles on rocks all teams engage in continuous battles collecting points on the way. Participants are tested on their programming skills and creativity, this online TEAM event is truly a treat far all tech geeks out their.</string>
    <string name="marath">An event that test how long you can persist solving the trickiest(and often the simplest) computer problems thrown at you. Doesnt require fluent coding skills as its logic based!!! A team event which is not to miss for all studednts from all branches and years.</string>
    <string name="rect">Feel you code can withdstand any challenge?Prove it! Requiring only a working nowledge of of C or C++, Rectify is an induvisual event which tests your skills in programming real world scenarios and is a must attend with its top coder challange coder.</string>
    <string name="ectf">Involving Crytography, Reverse engineering and Web app challanges and even Manipulating Security flaws, this Jeopardy style \"Capture the flag\" event is an online team competition where the ultimate goal is to find a specifically formatted dtring using the given resources efficiently and has participants from around the world.</string>
    <string name="antar">Antariksh is the space exhibition room of Astro Committee where the various projects undertaken by the club and models are displayed. Faculty members and students of the college, students from NITK school and visitors from other colleges attended the event. For more info about present year attractions click below!!</string>
    <string name="starwars">The annual Astro-Quiz held by Astro Committee was held on 13th October and the event saw around twenty teams participate for the prelims from which six qualified for the finals. The participants were thoroughly entertained and a cash prize of Rs. 2000 was awarded to the winners and Rs. 1000 to the runners-up.</string>
    <string name="Interst">The participants were provided with the problem statement two weeks in advance and were asked to construct a suitable lander which would carry a payload (an egg) and would be released from heights of 1.5, 5, 8 and 11m. The objective of the event was to assess the various safety mechanisms devised by the participants to protect the payload. The event was held on 15th October and a cash prize of Rs. 1500 was awarded to the winners.</string>
    <string name="endev">The event was conducted on 14th October where participants in groups of two or three were given a problem statement of human colonisation of a hypothetical planet, ‘Cyprian.’ Several constraints were provided such as atmospheric details and ground reserves of the planet and the planet’s distance from Earth. Each team had to come up with a solution to the problem statement while taking all the parameters into account. The two most optimal solutions were awarded a cash prize of Rs. 1250 and Rs. 750 respectively</string>
    <string name="starrynight">A trademark event for space enthusiasts to see all constellations,planets,moon and much more and find more about deep space</string>
    <string name="register">register</string>
</resources>
