<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Engineer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_menu">main_menu</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="EVENT_LIST_URL">http://www.engineernitk.org/schedule.php</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="schedule">Schedule</string>
    <string name="map">Map</string>

    <!--Home Page String                                             -->
    <string name="Tronix">Tronix</string>
    <string name="Mech">Mechanical</string>
    <string name="Meta">Metallurgy</string>
    <string name="Comp">Comp</string>
    <string name="chem">Reflux</string>
    <string name="Mining">Astro</string>
    <string name="Civil">Civil</string>
    <string name="Technites">Technites</string>
    <string name="title_sponsor">Title Sponsor</string>
    <string name="prizes_sponsor">Prizes Sponsor</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

    <string name="about_engi">Back in 2005, the marvels of NITK created a unique platform for the innovative minds to get acquainted to the aces of engineering industry. Multitude of students came together to organize the technical events and clubbed it into one grand glomeration and fondly christened it- ENGINEER, the annual technical symposium of NITK. Challenging the impossibility in the purest form, the Penrose triangle stands as the icon for the fest and so the maxim goes” THINK, CREATE, ENGINEER”.\nThe 14 th edition of Engineer far exceeds its ancestors, the fest emerges to be nationwide celebration, ranking second among India\'s technical fests. Racing its way to zenith, Engineer has become kaleidoscope of exhilaration of various flagship events such as Velocity, Robowar, Tronix Events, Workshops,flasmobs,online coding events with participation from various teams, among many such mind racking challenges. The stage has been enriched with the presence of distinguished speakers like Richard Stallman, Sam Pitrda, Dr Devi Sheet, Sir Anthony James Legett and many more. It has also played host to global organizations such as CERN, MIT Media and Ball Labs. To boost the effective innovation for the society, we also emphasise on Socially conscious Engineering. We also incorporate fun filled events like freefall which serve as pinnacle of attraction. NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY KARNATAKA This wonderful fusion of technical skills with boisterous events will definitely dilate the reasoning of innovative minds and helping them to showcase their talents on a higher platform.</string>
    <string name="foxhunt">Here we give you a chance to build your very own receiver antenna and compete with other Teams to hunt the Fox down.</string>
    <string name="Symphony">Taming a full-size fountain is no easy task. Yet, dozens of participants do exactly that,
        as they make the fountain dance to the beats of music </string>
    <string name="Trade_off">Show how frugal you can be, when you compromise between time and component costs to arrive at a circuit which gives the desired output?</string>
    <string name="TrailBlazer">Set the trail on fire (figuratively, please), as your bot goes around intricate curves following a line and performing tasks on the way</string>
    <string name="Light_of_seven">An event in which participants build a light following bot as the number of resources are lowered and its all about that</string>
    <string name="Automata">Automata is a competition where you are given a live feed from an overhead camera; the challenge is to autonomously make your computer guide your bot</string>
    <string name="Robowars">Robowars is an event in which participating teams battle it out among themselves with their bots for the numero uno position.</string>
    <string name="bot_hockey">Bot Hockey is an exciting and challenging competition featuring two teams with remote controlled robots competing against each other to score goals with a ball.</string>
    <string name="perfect_machine">Perfect machine is a unique competition which tests the skills of the participant in tackling various tasks that are given to them with their bot</string>
    <string name="wright_flight">Wright Flight attracts RC plane hobbyists from all over the country with unique and challenging flying tasks</string>
    <string name="bot_foot">Bot football is a multiplayer game where two players use their wire. less bots to defeat their opponent in a limited time football match.</string>
    <string name="laser_pro">Catch the eye-catching projects Laser Harp and Laser Turret which focuses on playing Harp with the turret</string>
    <string name="contr">A great implementation of classic Rube Goldberg machine.</string>
    <string name="virt_sand">This was most highly anticipated exhibition made by using Augmented Reality and used projector to implement it.</string>
    <string name="meta_mag">Showing the force of Metallurgy with Nylon Interfacial Condensation,Rod Climbing Experiment,Mercury Heartbeat and much more!</string>
    <string name="mindbend">A thrilling quiz with an interesting blend of pop culture, test your brain cells in this maze of questions that will surely bend your mind!</string>
    <string name="sem_tem">Participate in this guided tour through our labs and get to see how the Scanning and Transmission Electron Microscopes work.</string>
    <string name="constarch">This interactive session shows how crazy of a Non-Newtonian fluid constarch can be!</string>
    <string name="thermite">This extremely stunning visual demo shows the practical side of how welding rails work using the Thermite Welding process.</string>
    <string name="ga">Using pure science and a bit of brute force, embrittlement of Al sheets has never been explained easier in a way that triggers the brain.</string>
    <string name="blast_furnce">CDATA[A clay furnace and a low melting point metal such as Pb is all you need to show a successful demonstration. </string>
    <string name="foil">This dramatic session demonstrates how a simple packaging material like metal foil undergoes amalgamation.</string>
    <string name="col">The event is aimed to improve design and management skills of participants. And also provides an opportunity to learn fabrication processes.</string>
    <string name="mind_bend">The event will be an amalgamation of visual rounds and written tests, full of interesting and intriguing challenges</string>
    <string name="arch">BUILD SIMPLE, BUT WORKING MODELS FROM DAILY USE ITEMS(POPSICLE STICKS, PAPER ETC.). Civil Engineering is an art; a profession of creative ability and logic.</string>
    <string name="chem_break">It consists of a general quiz, a unique \'Picture Connect\' round and a treasure hunt as the final round which is conduted in the Chemical Dept. of NITK!!!</string>
    <string name="idp">IDP aims to enhance interaction with the industry through real time problem solving with problem statement given a week before</string>
    <string name="capture">Capture is a photo gallery event where you get to show us a moment captured by you, which depicts any science related processes.</string>
    <string name="chem_e_talks">Do you want to meet international academicians, researchers, entrepeneurs and industrialists? Then come join us at the Chem E talks</string>
    <string name="inscr">This individual flagship event online event has attracted participation from some of the top companies like Microsoft, Yahoo and from top competitive programmers</string>
    <string name="kode_komb">Three rounds, each being a thrilling mix of coding debugging and puzzles on rocks all teams engage in continuous battles collecting points on the way.</string>
    <string name="marath">An event that test how long you can persist solving the trickiest computer problems thrown at you and requires fluent coding skills as its logic based!!!</string>
    <string name="rect">Feel you code can withdstand any challenge?Prove it! Requiring only a working knowledge of C or C++, Rectify is an individual event</string>
    <string name="ectf">Involving Crytography, Reverse engineering and Web app challanges and even Manipulating Security flaws, this Jeopardy style "Capture the flag" event is an online team competition</string>
    <string name="antar">Antariksh is the space exhibition room of Astro Committee where the various projects undertaken by the club and models are displayed. </string>
    <string name="starwars">The annual Astro-Quiz held by Astro Committee was held on 13th October and the event saw around twenty teams participate for the prizes </string>
    <string name="Interst">The objective of the event is to assess the various safety mechanisms devised by the participants to protect the payload</string>
    <string name="endev">The event was conducted on 14th October where participants in groups of two or three were given a problem statement of human colonisation of a hypothetical planet</string>
    <string name="starrynight">A trademark event for space enthusiasts to see all constellations,planets,moon and much more and find more about deep space</string>
    <string name="register">register</string>

    <string name="banking_sponsor">Banking Sponsor</string>

</resources>
